{"data":[{"question":"Last December the boss gave all his ________ a bonus.","a":"employ","b":"employable","c":"employee","d":"employees","answer":"4","explain":"- To give somebody something\n- Employee: someone who is paid to work for someone else.\u00a0\n- All his + countable plural noun","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Are you sure we're going in the right ________?","a":"direct","b":"directly","c":"direction","d":"directed","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A\/an + adj + noun (noun phrase).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"My new car is more ________ than the one I had before.","a":"economy","b":"economical","c":"economic","d":"economics","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the comparative form of long adjective (economical)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"He works as an ________ for a local firm.","a":"electric","b":"electricity","c":"electrician","d":"electronic","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Electrician: someone whose job is to connect or repair electrical wires or equipment.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"I've been ________ since I must find work soon.","a":"unemployed","b":"employed","c":"employable","d":"unemployable","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Unemployed: without a job [= out of work].\u00a0\n- Unemployable: not having the skills or qualities needed to get a job.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"She studied ________ at university.","a":"economy","b":"economical","c":"economic","d":"economics","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Economics: the study of the way in which money and goods are produced and used.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The price of ________ has gone up again.","a":"electric","b":"electricity","c":"electrician","d":"electronic","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Electricity: the power that is carried by wires, cables..., and is used to provide light or heat, to make machines work.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Her ________ was so angry at her attitude that he fired her.","a":"employ","b":"employer","c":"employers","d":"employing","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Employer: a person, company, or organization that employs people.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"She looked ________ at me as she said it.","a":"direct","b":"directly","c":"direction","d":"directed","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Adverb modifies Normal verb (Look).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"On my salary we have to live as ________ as possible.","a":"economy","b":"economical","c":"economically","d":"economic","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Verb + as + adverb + as possible","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"}]}